Guide to the Margaret Meier Collection of Extreme Right Ephemeral Materials, 1930-1980
Department of Special Collections
Meier, Margaret, collector. Margaret Meier Collection of Extreme Right Ephemeral Materials,
1930-1980
M0688
Meier, Margaret, collector.
28 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Purchased, 1994.
Biography
Margaret and Herbert ("Herb") Meier were active in Republican politics in Orange County, and in California as a whole, primarily during the 1960s and 1970s. Herbert worked as a "field underwriter" at the Pasadena office of Home Life Insurance Co., of New York. Both were moderate Republicans, although Margaret held a membership card for the Moderate Democrats [see Box 20, folder 10]. In 1965, Herbert Meier was president of the Arcadia-Sierra Madre Chapter of the California Republican League, a "state-wide volunteer political organization authorized by the California Republican State Central Committee and activated in 1964," whose objective was that the "party must be broader, more dynamic, more forward-looking." Both Herbert and Margaret also held other state and local positions in Republican political groups. This collection reveals their effort to document the rise of the extreme right during these years.
Scope and Content
The Margaret Meier Collection of Extreme Right Ephemeral Materials, c1930-1980, consists of 47 manuscript boxes and 9 print boxes. The collection contains Margaret and Herbert Meier's materials documenting the rise and the activities of the extreme right in California and national politics. The bulk of the materials date from the 1960s-early 1970s, with additional materials from the late 1930s through the 1980s. Much of the materials relate to activities and groups in Southern California, where the Meiers lived, especially the towns of Arcadia and Sierra Madre. Included are political ephemera, newspaper and magazine clippings, and serials from extreme right groups such as the John Birch Society, Americanism clubs, various Christian right organizations, republican and extreme right political personalities. A censorship debate regarding the Arcadia Public Library's decision to include Kazantzakis' work, The Last Temptation of Christ, the activities of and opposition to the John Birch Society, and opposition to Senator Kuchel of California are three examples of subjects which are especially well covered. The collection also contains 18 boxes of serials and 3 OS boxes of newspapers, including publications of the John Birch Society and its leader, Robert Welch, the Institute for American Democracy, and Gerald L.K. Smith. MM's notes are found throughout the collection. The processors have made every attempt to retain MM's original order of the collection when possible, and have ordered the unorganized materials in this spirit.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Flournoy, Houston I. (Houston Irving), 1929-; Goff, Kenneth.; Goldwater, Barry M. (Barry Morris), 1909-; Kuchel, Thomas H.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-; Oliver, Revilo P. (Revilo Pendleton), 1910-; Reagan, Ronald.; Richardson, William.; Rousselot, John H.; Smith, Gerald L.K. (Gerald Lyman Kenneth), 1898-; Wallace, George C. (George Corley), 1919-; Arcadia Public Library.; John Birch Society.; Ku Klux Klan (1915- ); Republican Party (United States:1854- ); Republican Party (Calif.); Republican Party (Los Angeles County, Calif.); Republican Party (Los Angeles County, Calif.). Central.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American.; Young Republican National Federation (U.S.); American Opinion.; The Cross and the Flag.; Freedom Press.; Los Angeles Free Press.; Patriotic Review.; Anti-communist movements.; Antisemitism.; Censorship.; Civil Rights--United States.; Conservatism--United States--History--20th century.; Fundamentalism.; Right-wing extremists.; California--Politics and government--1951- .; United States--Politics and government--1945-1989.
Collection Contents
- Series 1. Subject Files
  Series 1, Subject Files, is arranged alphabetically by subject [issue, organization, person, event]. Most subject headings follow MM's original order of the collection. In cases where no logical order of the materials existed, additional subject headings were created during processing to allow for greater access. Types of materials included in the Subject Files include: extreme right political ephemera and newspaper and periodical clippings about issues [threat of communism, obscenity], people [Nixon, Robert Welch], or events [local and national elections].
  Pamphlets: Included under pamphlets are all non-serial publications that do not easily fit into a subject category. Serials are included here if they represent the only issue in this collection. The Pamphlets are arranged by alphabetical order, either by author, or if more logical, by title or publishing body.
  - A.B.C. (Alliance for a Better Community)1963-65 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    -see also ABC in Serials
  - A.C.L.U. - literature and clippings (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alert America Association (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Holmes Alexander - clippings (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Committee to Free Cuba (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Conservative Union (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Council of Christian Churches (Box 1, Folder 7)
    -see also Christian Group
  - American Council of Christian Laymen (Box 1, Folder 8)
    -see also Christian Groups
  - American Legion (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Nazi Party (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Opinion Bookstore - Santa Barbara (Box 1, Folder 11)
    -materials from bookstore; other materials from bookstore in specific subject files.
  - American Opinion Bookstore - Santa Barbara (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Opinion Bookstore - Sierra Madre (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Opinion Library - Costa Mesa (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Party (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Security Council (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Veterans Against Communism - Monrovia (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Americans for Constitutional Action (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Americans for National Security (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Americans United Council -- Long Beach1961-63 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Americanism clubs/schools (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Americanism Centers (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Americanism Educational League1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Eagle Rock Americanism Center (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Glendale Americanism School (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Monterey Park Americanism Center (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - South Pasadena Americanism School (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - America's Future, Inc. (education org.) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Anti-Communist Voters League (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith (ADL) (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - see Watchdog Groups--1980-90s
  - Anti-Red Schools (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Semitism (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Semitism (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Semitism-Clippings (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Semitism-Clippings (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - JBS Anti-Semitic and Racist Materials (Box 2, Folder 6)
    -see JBS
  - Arcadia City Council Race, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Arcadia Educational Forum (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Arcadia Love-In (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Arcadia Public Library Controversy. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    This group of materials focuses on the fight to censor Kazantzakis' book The Last Temptation of Christ in the Arcadia Public library, 1962-64. Included are correspondence, minutes from Arcadia Library Board of Trustees, clippings and articles, and related material about censorship/freedom of speech. The controversy reflected the different stands of the moderate and radical Christian right in the town. -see also Censorship
  - Arcadia Library Controversy; Arcadia Library (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 0)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Arcadia Library Board of Trustees (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Arcadia Library Annual Reports1962-64 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (folder marked "Mrs. Kirkpatrick") (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy -clippings (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy -Meiers' personal correspondence (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy-City Council decision (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy-Calif. Library Assoc. Intellectual Freedom Kit1963 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy-Library Rules (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Arcadia Library Controversy-ALA Bulletins with reference to Arcadia Controversy (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Jim Arditto (CA lawyer, Democrat) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Average Citizens' Study Group - Monrovia (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Banned Book Catalogue (Box 5, Folder 6)
    -see also Obscenity, Censorship
  - Bombings (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - William F. Buckley, Jr. -clippings1964-67 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Burbank Library--Censorship-Clippings1962-63 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - California Groups (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - California Committee to Combat Communism (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - California Committee to Combat Communism (Box 5, Folder 13)
    --Clippings
  - California Republican Assembly 1962-66 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - California Republican Assembly 1962-66 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - California Republican Assembly 1966-67 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - California Republican League1964-66 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - California Republican League1964-66 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - California Republican League1964-66 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - California Teachers' Association (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Candidates (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cartoons (political cartoon clippings) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Issues (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Censorship-see also Arcadia Library Controversy, Obscenity (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Censorship-Clippings (Book Banning) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Censorship-Clippings (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Censorship-Clippings Christian Groups in alphabetical order (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Christian Citizen (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Christian Crusade-Clippings (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Christian Crusade-Literature (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Christian Defense League-Clippings (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Christian Freedom Foundation (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Christian Resistance (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Christian Science--Clippings (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Christian Youth Against Communism (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Church/Christian Right (lit. and clippings) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Church/Christian Literature (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Churches (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Church Leagues of America (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Circuit Riders, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Citizens' Committee of California--Clippings (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Citizens' Comm. of CA--Literature (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - (including Grassroots & Countdown) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Citizens for Decent Literature-Clippings (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Citrus Americanism Center (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Citrus Americanism Center (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - City of Arcadia - Library Board of Trustees (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - City Council A.R.G. - Monrovia (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Civil Rights (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Clean Initiative-see also Censorship (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Coast Federal Savings (Bank) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Paul Coates (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cold War Council (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Committee of Christian Laymen (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Committee for a Responsible Supreme Court (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Communists and Communism, general (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Communists--Clippings (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Communists--Clippings (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Communist goods and merchandise (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Communist goods-Clippings (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Conservatives (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Conservative Society of America; other conservative groups (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Constructive Report (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - M. Meier (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Father Charles Coughlin (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Council on American Relations (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - County and State Central Committee (Republicans) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Alan Cranston (1968) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Cranston's report against JBS-see JBS (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Cranston on Reagan - (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Cuba (1962-63, clippings) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - D.A.C.A. (Drive Against Communist Aggression) and Guy Gabaldon (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - D.A.R. (Daughters of the American Revolution)-Literature (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - D.A.R.-Clippings (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Democrats (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Dental and Doctor Groups (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Clarence Desmond (Columnist) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Dictionary of American Slang Censorship (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Education (text book guidelines, curriculum disputes, local/fed'l control) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Education (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Education (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Education (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Education (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Education Information, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Episcopal Church (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Episcopalians (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Episcopalians (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Episcopalian Ascension Church of Sierra Madre (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Episcopalian Right Wing (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Episcopalian Right Wing (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Episcopalian Right Wing (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Extreme Right Wing --see also Institute of (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - American Democracy, JBS, and Extreme Right materials in OS Box 3 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Extreme Right Wing 1962-70 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Extreme Right Wing, incl. Goldwater1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Extreme Right Wing1980-90s (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Extreme Right Wing1990s (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Extreme Right Wing -Clippings (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Extreme Right Wing -Clippings (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Extreme Right Wing (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Extreme Right Wing (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Extreme Right Wing (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Extreme Right Wing Politicians - Clippings1978-87 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Papers and Studies on Extreme Right by Moderates (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Extreme Right/Anti-Communist (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Extreme Right/Anti-Communist (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Extreme Right/Anti-Communist (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Extreme Right/Anti-Communist (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Extreme Right/Anti-Communist (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Extreme Right/Anti-Communist (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Extreme Right/Anti-Communist (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Extreme Right/Anti-Communist (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Extreme Right/Anti-Communist (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Extremists (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Extremists -Labor (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - FBI (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Dr. James Fifield, Jr. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 54th Assembly District (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Fire and Police Research Association of L.A. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Fire and Police Research Association of L.A -Clippings (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Hugh (Houston) Flournoy (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Flournoy -Correspondence w/Meiers (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Flournoy -Clippings (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Fluoridization (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - F.O.R.E. (Force for an Organized (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Responsible Electorate). Includes FORECAST newsletter, 1964-67 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - F.O.R.E. -Clippings1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Aid (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Calvin Fox -Correspondence (perhaps rel'd (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - to Kuchel) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Francis Amendment (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Patrick Frawley -Clippings (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Free Enterprise Bureau -see also Coast Fed'l (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Savings (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Free Society Association (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Free Speech Controversy - U.C. Berkeley (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Freedom Dynamics (org. supporting (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Free World youth festival) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Freedom University on the Air (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Freedoms Foundationca.1963-67 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Fund for the Republic (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Buell Gallagher (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Girl Scouts (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Kenneth Goff (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Kenneth Goff -Literature (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Kenneth Goff -Pamphlets (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Kenneth Goff -Pamphlets (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Kenneth Goff -Clippings (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Barry Goldwater -Campaign Materials (Box 13, Folder 1)
    1964
  - Goldwater -Campaign Materials. Includes campaign newsletter1964. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Goldwater -supporters (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Goldwater -supporters (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Goldwater -extremists (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Goldwater -literature, editorials (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Goldwater -literature, editorials (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Goldwater -Clippings (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Goldwater -Clippings (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Goldwater -Magazine clippings (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Goldwater -Clippings and pamphlets (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Goldwater -Clippings, S. Calif. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Goldwater -Clippings, S. Calif. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Goldwater -Clippings, Arcadia, CA (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Goldwater-Letters to Arcadia Times, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Goldwater -Publications:--Nat'l Observer Newsbook --I Seek an America1964 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Groups and Organizations -M.Meier's lists (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Groups and Organizations (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Groups and Organizations (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Gun Laws (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - John W. Harvey (Monrovia Patriotic Observance Committee) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Hate Groups -see Watchdog Groups (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Edgar Hiestand (Congressman) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - HUAC (House Un-American Activities Committee) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - HUAC -Publications (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - HUAC -Clippings (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Institute for American Democracy -see also (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Special Research - George Robnett, Pasadena (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - John Birch Society (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - The Meiers collected information on the John Birch Society in their aim of documenting the growth of the radical right in American politics. These materials are very loosely organized by subheadings; it is suggested that researchers interested in the JBS scan all folders under the heading JBS. Because of the wide scope of this organization, additional information about the JBS can be found under other subject headings.
  - JBS (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - JBS -Civil Rights Mov't pamphlets distributed by JBS (from folder "JBS Pamphlets") (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - JBS -Civil Rights materials (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - JBS -Anti-communist pamphlets distributed by (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - JBS (from folder "JBS anti-communist") (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - JBS - Anti-communist literature (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - JBS - Anti-communist literature (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - JBS - M.Meier's notes, pamphlets (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - JBS -Cranston report, MM notes (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - JBS -"None Dare Call it Reason/Treason" (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - JBS -Pink Book of the JBS for 1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    1963
  - JBS -Committee for a Responsible Supreme Court (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - JBS -Committee for a Responsible Supreme Court (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - JBS -and GOP (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - JBS -American Opinion Speakers' Bureau (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - JBS -Pamphlets and reprints1958 - 1966 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Pageant (JBS v. police, p. 68)Robert Welch. Reflections on the Elections1964 Rousselot. Disarmament 1963 J.B. Matthews. The World Health Organization (2 copies) 1958 D.C. Manion. This is where I came in. 1960 R.P. Oliver. The Black Muslims. 1963 J.E. Coogan. American Catholics- a household divided? (2 copies ) 1962 R. Welch. Through all the days to be. 1961
  - JBS -literature (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - JBS 1961-62 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - JBS -Clippings (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - JBS -Clippings1980s-90s (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - JBS-JBS Meetings and Young Republicans (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - JBS-JBS Meetings and LA Young Republicans (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - JBS-Clippings on members and meetings1961-63 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - JBS-Calif. Report, members; testimonial dinner 1963-65 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - JBS-Clippings, Meetings, Members1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - JBS-Clippings and Notes1963-74 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - JBS-Clippings1965 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - JBS-Clippings1966-67 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - JBS-Clippings1968-69 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - JBS1963-65 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - JBS (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - JBS (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson - 1964 Election Clippings 1964- (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Katanga (African Congo and UN action) Kennedy Assassination (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Ku Klux Klan (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Ku Klux Klan (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Senator Kuchel (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kuchel - Surveillance of LA Young Republicans, Max Rafferty (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Speech by Kuchel,(The Fright Peddlars) May 2, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Kuchel Speech -response (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kuchel Speech - response Congressional Record (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Kuchel Speech - anti-semitic/racist responses (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kuchel Speech - anti-semitic/racist responses (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Kuchel Speech - anti-semitic/racist responses (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Kuchel Speech - anti-semitic/racist responses (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Kuchel Speech - rightist responses (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Kuchel Speech - responses (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Kuchel Speech - responses (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Kuchel Speech - response in press (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Kuchel (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Kuchel (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Kuchel -Clippings (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Kuchel -Clippings (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - L.A. County Commission on Human Relations (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - L.A. Riots (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Land of the Free Text Book (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Land of the Free Text Book (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Lyndon LaRouche - Clippings1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - 'Last Temptation of Christ' (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - League of Women Voters, 1 article (Box 18, Folder 11)